"Healthy Seongsu Man."
(Healthy Seongsu Man's New Challenge)
How am I going to organize everything?
Let me fold the laundry first.
(His dressing room is cluttered with clothes.)
You have a lot of clothes.
I just can't seem to organize them.
I ought to pay you a visit.
You really love the hospital shade of green.
It's deep green.
(They seem to be organized and chaotic at the same time.)
Once my clothes started to pile up,
I gradually gave up on keeping them tidy.
They began to turn into a mess and I neglected the mess.
So my dressing room is the least organized room now.
I just throw everything I don't want to see in that room.
- Of course. - Everyone does that.
Well, it's like a pancreas.
- What? - A pancreas?
Things get filtered through there.
You studied a lot about medicine...
since you live in Severance Hospital.
I found out about the function of pancreas...
- just now. - Same here.
(The color of knowledge in 2026, deep green)
Gosh, what do I do?
- You should bring everything down. - Seriously?
- You must do it without any regret. - Right.
Getting started is always tough.
Right. Once you get started, it goes smoothly.
Right.
That too...
I don't know where to begin.
(Grabbing)
This...
(Glancing up)
Sweater.
Is it a short sleeve shirt?
Short sleeve shirt. Hoodie.
It will take forever at that rate.
Long sleeve shirt.
Hoodie.
I wanted to get rid of my old clothes.
That crossed my mind.
I didn't wear some of those clothes for a year...
which means I won't wear them.
So I decided to follow my gut and make quick decisions...
while going through my clothes.
Once I saw fit to throw out certain clothes,
I decided to sort them out without hesitation.
(He starts sorting out clothes that need to be thrown out.)
Gosh, you'll pick and choose?
I was going to throw out some old clothes without hesitation.
(Let me see.)
I wore this for a long time.
Since I wore it for a long time...
Bye.
(Tossing)
These too.
I'll throw out most of them.
This process will make you more thoughtful when buying clothes.
- Right. - Yes.
Green pants.
I might wear them at some point.
I can't throw out deep green pants. I'll keep them.
(Deep green shorts survive.)
They are comfortable too.
Here's the sentence that tempts you the most when throwing out clothes.
"I'll wear them at home."
- "I'll wear them as pajamas." - Yes. "I'll wear them as pajamas."
That's the most dangerous one.
(Thinking)
I'll probably wear them as pajamas.
(Embarrassed)
Pants.
(Unfolding)
Aren't they all the same pants?
Aren't they all pajamas?
(They do look similar.)
I don't want any of your clothes.
I usually go crazy for clothes.
You should get rid of everything since you won't wear any of them.
Then what am I going to wear if I do that?
I usually think, "Why is he throwing them out?"
"What a waste."
- But nothing really stands out. - You can stay calm, right?
- Right. Looking at his clothes... - Same here.
He and I basically have the same clothes.
Then you sorted out your clothes too?
Clothes even I won't wear...
- must be thrown out. - Right.
I see a lot of such clothes in his room.
I took a look at his room. He's in a pretty tough situation.
Short sleeve shirts.
You need to do a good job with short sleeve shirts.
Start from number one.
Go to number three and grab it.
Turn it.
After turning it...
- What? - You see that in clothing stores.
- There. - I see.
I'll fold this one more time.
That's neat.
How did you do that?
- That's the retail-style fold. - How interesting.
That's the first thing you learn while working at clothing stores.
(Leaning forward)
- I bet there are 1,000 of them. - Right.
I used to work briefly in a clothing store...
- Really? - a long time ago.
I have my own method of folding clothes. It only takes a second.
- Do it. - How?
- I don't buy that. One second? - You grab it.
- And then? - Then you do this.
Then you do this.
- What? - How...
You're just folding it in half.
(Puzzled)
Let's do it with a T-shirt.
- I'm so curious. I must see it. - I'm curious.
I see. That?
Gosh, that's...
- Wait. I... - You're stripping down Wilson.
- Will it work with that? - Let's learn it.
- Will it work with a hoodie? - So...
- One-second fold. - Gosh, it will take a second.
- Because it's a hoodie? - Let's watch.
(All eyes are on him.)
(Those of you who had a tough time folding clothes, )
(check out my 1-second secret method.)
All right. Go ahead.
- Are you done shopping? - Yes.
Like that.
- What is that? - Hey. What is this?
(Looking like messy laundry)
- What is that? - That's really iffy.
It's all crumpled up.
Right. With my method, it's not as neat as it should be.
- Is it because it's a hoodie? - So...
there are just so many clothes to organize.
(Trying to understand him)
(His 1-second secret method is to fold clothes half-heartedly.)
(Try my method. It's easy.)
I'll put them back.
(Putting away folded clothes)
- That looks neat now. - You created more space now.
- Yes. You must've thrown out half. - That's good.
Great.
That's good.
(This time, he goes through his jackets.)
This is good.
(What's this jacket?)
I rarely wear coats.
You can film a period piece with it.
I doubt I'll wear it.
- A suit. - I hardly ever wear coats.
- That one looks good. - This one looks nice.
- It's nice. It looks good on you. - Really?
- You should keep it. - But it's slightly big on you.
I should throw it out too.
I'll let it go.
- No. Not that one. - What a pity.
- I don't have an eye for this. - That one looked nice.
You really don't.
What if you only threw out good ones?
(Oh, no)
The most important point is that I must exclude my emotions.
"My ex-girlfriend gave it to me as a birthday present."
"My mom gave it to me as a present at my high school graduation."
Then I won't be able to throw out anything.
But I must throw them out for my mom to buy me more clothes.
I must throw them out, so I can get a new girlfriend.
That's the logic.
(Looking for a girlfriend)
Are you challenging me?
The worst son this country has ever seen.
Why throw out a present from your mom?
That way, she'll buy him more.
I think this will be a good match.
You're catching up fast.
So his mom can buy him more.
I'm done picking out clothes to throw out. After this...
I threw out a lot of clothes.
(A bag full of clothes)
(Gosh, I'm finally done.)
(Before and after the cleaning session)
- What has changed? - Wait. That's...
- His shelves look a bit empty now. - Righit.
He's gotten more space now.
(Looking clean)
Let me weigh this.
(Tossing)
(Stepping on it)
It's 64.5kg.
You're skinny.
(He steps on the scale again with the bag.)
It weighs 15kg.
- Why are you weighing it? - It's 15kg.
Can you accumulate points?
(The 1st bag weighs 15kg.)
It's 10kg.
(The 2nd bag weighs 10kg.)
It's 5kg.
(The 3rd bag weighs 5kg.)
That's 30kg in total.
My gosh.
So it's 30kg. I can do this.
Okay. Let's go then.
(Sounding determined)
(He grabs the bags...)
(and goes out briskly.)
You're carrying 30kg?
- It must hurt his shoulders. - Right.
Why didn't you take your car? Why walk?
(Ju Seung is heading somewhere on foot.)
After watching the episode, the Grand Rainbow Bazaar,
- I also wanted to donate. - That's good.
- I was motivated to donate too. - That's great.
I'm heading to a charity shop for secondhand items.
That's good.
The shop isn't that far away.
So I wanted to walk there.
On my way there, I wanted to look around my neighborhood again.
There are some things you see...
- when you take your time. - Right.
I decided to walk there...
because it'd be a nice chance to look around too.
So I don't need to throw them out in the clothing box.
I didn't bring clothes I was going to throw out.
- I took clothes in good condition. - Right.
- I see. - On purpose?
(He walks while looking around the neighborhood.)
My gosh, 30kg...
is...
heavier than I thought.
- That's really heavy. - Right, it's so heavy.
That's as heavy as full combat gear.
(Exhaling)
This is all part of my training.
(He's been through a good number of intensive training.)
(Today is just one of those training days.)
He's Martial Artist Ju Seung.
- It's a nice workout too. - Great.
(This is a piece of cake.)
(Exhaling)
All right.
The straps were digging into my shoulders quite painfully.
- I bet. - You know what I mean, right?
- The straps were digging into them. - It hurts.
That was really painful.
Gosh, that must've been really tough.
It must be tough.
(Staggering)
(The more he walks, )
(the heavier his steps feel.)
- You should've taken a local bus. - It would've been so heavy.
(Feeling sorry for him)
(Slow)
(Pausing)
- What's that? - What is it?
- It was someone's underwear. - What?
(Abandoned on the street)
- What? - How could that happen?
- How... - I doubt someone took off...
his underwear there.
Probably not.
I've never seen underwear on the street like that.
It's my first time too.
- Totally. - Right.
- And it doesn't even look dirty. - And...
on top of that, the underwear has a daring color scheme.
Usually, the waistband is white, and the underwear is black.
But it's the other way around.
Right. It also looks like...
- someone recently wore it. - Right.
- That's hilarious. - Why are we analyzing this?
It's like this is staged.
- I'm curious too. - Gosh, that's...
(How did it end up there?)
This is crazy.
Someone must've taken it off there.
I didn't know what to do, so I walked past it.
- Right. It's weird to pick it up. - Did someone leave it behind?
It belongs to someone.
I shouldn't pick it up.
The owner might come back for it.
It must've fallen from a laundry rack.
(It must've fallen from a laundry rack.)
(He keeps on moving, leaving behind the lost underwear.)
(Struggling)
What's that?
(This time, it's a top.)
- What? - Someone who's donating clothes...
- Seriously? What? - must have dropped it.
- What's happening? - What is this?
He might have taken off his clothes while walking.
Right. That's possible. He must've been drunk.
Like the story, Hansel and Gretel?
He must not like how the city was boxing him in.
- He marked his territory. - Seriously. This is crazy.
It's like the game, "Battlegrounds."
- Right? - Yes.
- Picking things up one at a time. - He's farming.
- He can't take that off first. - You should've bought some then.
He must've taken them off one at a time looking at the combo.
I saw all kinds of weird things when I walked to the shop.
This is hilarious. Seriously.
Someone who's donating clothes...
must have dropped it.
If you're lucky, you could get an entire outfit from there.
(If you're lucky, you could get an entire outfit from there.)
I should have ridden my bicycle here. My gosh.
I didn't know it would be this far.
You're on a full-on march.
Gosh, that must be really heavy.
It's got to be really heavy.
(Exhausted)
- Wait. - There's another one?
No way.
- Wait. - It's a handcart.
- My gosh. - There's a cart.
- Borrow it. - Can you use it?
It's like he's playing a game. He keeps finding items.
- Right. Seriously. - You're right.
- This is Battlegrounds. - What's happening?
It looks like he's inside a game.
What's the cart doing there?
There are a lot of lighting stores and hardware stores.
So they use carts to carry things.
See if you can borrow it.
(A handcart from a nearby lighting or hardware store)
Should I borrow it?
(I can't carry them like this anymore.)
(He musters up his courage and enters.)
- Hello. - Hi.
I'm sorry to be asking you for this.
But could I borrow your cart?
- It won't take long. - Sure.
Thank you. I have some things...
- to carry. - He's a nice guy.
You're good with people.
Thank you.
I'll bring it right back. It will only take ten minutes.
What a relief.
What a lifesaver.
(Relieved)
Gosh, it's so easy now.
- This is the best. - You should've started with a cart.
- Exactly. - Totally.
- I really needed it. - The lighting store owner...
is a lifesaver.
(This was just what he needed.)
Thank you, Mr. Lighting Store Owner.
- I bet it was hot. - It got so hot.
(He arrives in a hurry.)
Did you arrive? You arrived.
I see. They also sell things here.
- My gosh. - Oh, my.
I know the place too.
It's famous.
They sell clothes, plates, and books.
- They sell all kinds of things. - Yes, they do.
- Did you... - How nice.
So they would donate the profits...
- from the store? - They'd donate it.
- My gosh. - It's a virtuous cycle.
- Sort them out and count them. - Sure. You got it.
I see. That's how it's done.
- Let me go... - Yes.
- and return this quickly. - Sure.
I told him I'd bring it back in ten minutes.
(While his clothes are being examined, )
(he rushes over to the lighting store.)
(Parking it)
- Sir, I brought it back. - Okay.
I brought something. I wanted to thank you.
- They're some bread and cookies. - No.
- Thank you. I just bought them. - Gosh, no.
- Gosh, no. - I just bought them.
- I was so grateful. I left quickly. - Thank you.
- Thank you. - That's nice of you.
I bought him some cookies.
That must be a load off your chest.
Right. That was a load off my chest.
(He arrives back at the store while feeling relieved.)
I wonder how much they would come out to.
(Curious)
- Could you check on that? - Yes.
- Is it all done? - Yes.
All of your clothes were in good condition.
- Really? - I see.
- Come and take a look at this. - Yes.
- We'll get you registered. - Okay.
- Then... - Gosh.
- That's a lot of clothes. - Seriously.
Then will it get donated under your name?
Yes. The amount will be calculated later.
- How much did it come out to? - How much did it come out to?
It was over 210 dollars.
That's a good number.
It's much better than throwing them out.
- Much better. - It's much better.
- Thank you. - Sure.
- I'll come back often. - Okay.
When people go there to shop, they'll probably buy something.
It's a virtuous cycle.
It's getting slightly chilly since my sweat is cooling off.
(Ju Seung is going somewhere in a hurry.)
I wonder where he's going next.
(Striding in)
Is he going to exercise?
- What's this? - It's a clothing shop.
A vintage shop?
(A huge clothing shop located in the basement)
Hello.
- Hello. - It's been a while.
"It's been a while?"
Since I got rid of a lot of clothes,
- I should get some more. - On the same day?
It's the vintage store I often shop at.
You'll buy more vintage clothes after donating your old clothes?
Right. I'll go all vintage.
I think you'll end up at the store pretty soon.
This routine might be an endless cycle.
You're such a kind, young man.
Lately, I've been interested in fashion.
I've been thinking a lot about my fashion style.
I usually wear whatever I can find.
There's no right answer in fashion.
I'm in the process of learning about fashion.
(He goes through the racks and studies them.)
This looks warm.
- You startled me. What on earth? - Who's that?
When did you get here?
He's a friend of mine. He's an actor and his name is Son Woo Hyeon.
We met three years ago when we worked on a play,
"Tebas Land," together.
- That's when you guys bonded. - Yes.
We hang out often since we live closeby.
(He's become Ju Seung's best friend.)
I've spent the most time with him over the past three years.
He's the closest actor friend I have.
He's popular on Instagram because he has...
the kind of the boyfriend look women like.
Among my friends, he's most interested in fashion.
- He's stylish. - Gosh, he's handsome.
He takes good pictures.
He knows a lot about how to look stylish.
He has a good body proportion.
- Of course. - He was second only...
- Yes. - to Sungsimdang in popularity.
- Really? He's from Daejeon. - I heard it from someone else.
- Because of his looks? - Because of his looks.
(He was famous for his looks.)
When I go shopping with him,
I can learn a lot from him.
So I'm taking a lesson today.
I already looked through this rack.
- You did? - Yes.
What happened to your shoes?
Did you just come from a restaurant where you had to take them off?
- Why are your shoelaces undone? - I did that on purpose.
I took out the tongues on purpose.
- So... - I wanted the effortless look.
- I see. Is that trending? - Effortless like I'm not trying.
- You're walking around like that? - Yes, I am.
You know what?
Even an outfit like that looks good on fashionable people.
That's true.
But if people like us wear that kind of outfit...
"People like us?"
- You're drawing the line. - But...
- You're not fashionable either. - What?
- CO KUN is stylish. - Right.
He's a fashionista.
You're not fashionable either.
Me?
- What are you talking about? - You're not fashionable.
- Kian84 suddenly got serious. - What's wrong with you?
I feel offended getting that kind of comment from you.
I didn't expect him to react like this.
Why are you, of all people, talking about fashion?
(Chuckling)
Gosh, this is so upsetting.
Hey.
I dressed up for the show today.
- You're wearing a nice outfit. - You look good today.
- You look stylish today. - You look great.
- Woo Il. Okay. - This is your best outfit so far.
- Let's check it out. - Let's look.
Let's check out what they have.
I...
(Quickly scanning)
The last cold spell is coming soon.
You can wear a jacket like this.
You always told me...
- to rip the bottom. - Right.
- There are two zippers. - Yes.
Here's how you wear it.
- All the way up? - Here.
- Zip it up completely? - Once you zip it up,
you can unzip the bottom one like this.
- Okay. - Here you go.
Red looks great on you.
Will this make my legs look longer?
- Right. Your legs will look longer. - I see.
Right. Your legs do look longer.
(I knew I could count on my fashion coach.)
- Hey, Ju Seung. - Okay.
(They look for another item after the red zip-up sweater.)
I came across this style.
- There's a new term, "poetcore." - Poetcore?
- Poetcore? - What's that?
Poetcore.
It's a compound word of poet and core.
(Teaching him about a new fashion trend)
- It's the artist or the poet look. - Like a man...
standing under a zelkova tree...
- That's right. - with glasses.
This style suits Jung Hoon.
- Choi Jung Hoon? - And Jong Won too.
- So someone with that paper vibe? - Right.
- I see. - And you also write.
- You're a writer. - I do.
I thought this would suit you well too.
- I'd like to try that too. - Right.
- It looks pretty cool. - I'm after poetcore now.
You are?
The trend ended almost as soon as it started.
(Browsing)
Do you want to try this on?
Just throw that on.
- On this shirt? - Yes.
That looks good on you.
(Putting on a button-down shirt his coach picked out)
- The color suits you too. - With that shirt,
He's good at this.
You could wear a pair of pants like this one.
- Like this. - Okay.
After this, we should...
- It's for the poetcore look, right? - Yes.
Your outfit would look nice with a blazer or something.
- I doubt he knows what it is. - What's that?
- A jacket. - There's no way he'd know.
Something like this.
- I think it will look good on you. - This one?
Yes. This one. Try it on.
Yes. Put that on.
- Let me try them on fast. - Okay.
(He goes to the fitting room with clothes his coach picked out.)
(Meanwhile, his coach places more clothes on the rack.)
(The coach selects other outfits in advance too.)
- Hey. - What?
- Hold on. - I don't think this is the look.
Wait.
Don't I look like Woong's dad?
- Wait. Right. - You look like an old poet.
You look like you'd smoke a pipe.
Shin-chan's dad often wears T-shirts like that.
- Right. - Shin-chan's dad.
You keep getting new characters.
Wait. This isn't what I had in mind. Here's the key point of the outfit.
But you look good.
It doesn't look that bad. You just feel awkward.
This is a new style for you. Have you worn an outfit like this before?
No. I haven't. But...
(I can't laugh now.)
I thought he sneezed. But he was laughing.
You haven't, right? So put on some glasses.
(Trying to remedy the situation fast)
(The glasses?)
Fold the collar neatly.
- I should... Okay. - Yes, pull it down.
Let me put a scarf on you. Grab it and wrap it around you.
(This isn't the vibe I was looking for.)
(Even the fashion teacher shakes his head.)
He looks like the owner of a used bookstore.
The most stubborn one.
He looks like a new student in the "Harry Potter" series.
There must be a style that suits him better...
- than that outfit. - I know. You shouldn't copy styles.
He should find the Ju Seung-core aesthetic.
- Ju Seung, you have unique vibes. - That's right.
You need to accentuate them,
not hide them.
(My vibes?)
You know the basic light blue shirt, right?
The basic sky blue shirt.
Yes.
Ju Seung wore a shirt like that when we went to Gyeongju.
No one here looks better in it than you.
- I agree. - That's right.
I thought you looked cool back then.
In my opinion,
- he looks better with fewer layers. - That's right.
- That's what I'm saying. - Exactly.
He shouldn't go for many layers. I'm the same.
- He needs to relax. - That's right.
Since you have respectable looks,
you should go for street fashion.
- You should wear hip jeans. - Hip fashion.
You'd look good in such items.
They'd transform your image.
- You need to find your own style. - Of course.
That's right. I haven't found it yet,
so I'm trying various things.
Poetcore is a bit hard to pull off.
Let's go for younger looks.
- Younger looks? - Yes.
Let's go for the hip street vibes.
- Woo Il had the same opinion. - Yes.
This one.
(Will this suit him better?)
- This one? - Cargo pants.
A fitted jacket. How about this one?
(Let's see.)
This one is nice.
(A basic top)
Put them on while I look for more items.
(This time as well, he quickly puts together an outfit.)
(Lastly, he finds street-style shoes.)
- Shoes too. - Shoes are important.
- That's right. - Shoes are very important.
That's right. Shoes are so important.
Woo Hyeon, these pants...
Yes?
They're big, right?
They aren't just big.
I could fit Coco in here.
Sagging style is in vogue these days.
Saggang?
- Sagging. - Sagging.
- Sagging? - Sagging.
It's a trend where pants are worn below the waist to show the butt.
It was a popular street fashion back in the day.
(A fashion trend that reveals the underwear)
Does it look hip?
- Does it look effortless? - Effortless.
- Looking effortless is important. - Effortless is good.
We like effortless style.
- Hyun Moo likes it too. - I like effortless style too.
Fashionistas like effortless style.
Effortless.
If you look at my pants, they're below the waist...
like this.
- This much underwear is showing. - My underwear is showing too.
My pants are slung low.
Isn't he practically taking off his pants?
He has belly fat.
You should've changed into different underwear.
Your underwear doesn't look hip.
It doesn't have a waistband.
That's right. You need strong underwear for that style.
If you wear your pants like this,
your outfit looks effortless and natural.
(A bit uncertain)
Why doesn't this outfit look good?
(Why doesn't this outfit look good?)
Should it be tucked in?
(The fashion lesson gets stuck.)
Should it be tucked in or not?
Gosh, this isn't the vibe.
(Nervous)
I think I picked the wrong pants.
Let me try on that outfit.
Let me do that.
Are you guys switching outfits?
He's checking if the problem is the outfit or the person.
It's so...
(Opening)
(Staggering)
That T-shirt suits Ju Seung the most.
A white T-shirt.
Ju Seung, let's wear that 365 days a year.
- Your face looks brighter. - Your personal color must be white.
A basic T-shirt.
A basic T-shirt suits you the most.
- I'll buy you ten. - You know, the B brand one.
(This won't do.)
This is...
(Opening)
That's it.
(What?)
This is...
(Opening)
That's it.
(What?)
For the sagging trend, pull down the pants a bit...
so that your belt is showing.
- He looks cool. - You know...
It's a nice outfit.
He definitely looks different.
Show it like this.
A natural style is popular these days.
- My goodness. - He looks cool.
That's the boyfriend aesthetics on many people's minds.
Boyfriend with filters.
The real boyfriend aesthetics.
It's a hip outfit.
Boyfriend without filters.
(Ju Seung is the boyfriend without filters.)
You're so mean.
On social media, you see Woo Hyeon.
- In real life, you see Ju Seung. - That's right.
Filters.
- His standards are too high. - That's right.
When you need fashion advice,
you should ask someone similar.
- That's right. - As for someone like him,
- That's right. - he looks good...
in the underwear and T-shirt you saw on the street.
- I agree. - You're right.
- Like modern art. - You're right.
I have an idea.
Do you want to try on a beanie?
You looked good in a beanie.
(He puts on a beanie, a street fashion item.)
He looks good in a beanie.
- I think he looks good. - Yes.
- He looks good in a beanie. - It's a nice addition.
The eyebrows... That's right. You look good now.
You look like a rapper.
What do you think?
There you go.
(He moves with a swagger like a rapper.)
You can groove like this.
- That's a nice outfit. - Like this.
- That's a nice outfit. - I know.
You look good in a beanie.
We're disappointed about the sagging style, right?
I think it'll suit you since you look good in a beanie.
So let's put on two pants.
Let's go.
- What? Two pants? - Yes. Let's go.
I did that when I sleepwalked in the military.
This pair goes inside and this pair goes outside.
Two pants?
(Did you think I was wearing one pair of pants?)
(Two pairs of pants)
TARZZAN wears pants like that.
(TARZZAN of ALLDAY PROJECT wears pants like that.)
I realized something about fashion upon moving to Seoul.
When someone dresses in a bizarre way,
people call him a fashionista.
It's true.
Trot singers don't go for the sagging style, right?
Of course not.
If anyone does that, it'll be a disaster.
It'll be a disaster.
It'll be a broadcasting accident.
- Middle-aged women will be shocked. - Of course.
Like this.
When I wear clothes like this,
- my posture... - It changes, right?
My body...
leans forward.
(He charges forward with confidence.)
Effortless.
He looks good in a photo.
He looks like he'll enter "Show Me the Money."
Not bad.
I think it's nice.
It's really nice. Let's put on this outfit too.
(With the heightened spirits, he tries on the next outfit.)
It's nice. It's effortless.
(Flapping)
I think it suits me.
The sagging fashion suits me.
It looks more natural than the poetcore fashion.
Since he has gained confidence, we're getting fooled.
He looks cool.
Here's what I think.
You talked about JUHOON of CORTIS.
So I think it'll be nice...
- to go for a similar look. - His answer changed.
You look like you could be JUHOON's older cousin.
Try on this outfit.
There's an idol group called CORTIS.
People tell me that I resemble a member named JUHOON.
(JUHOON of CORTIS, a rookie idol group)
(JUHOON of CORTIS looks like Ju Seung.)
(Doesn't JUHOON look a bit like Ju Seung?)
(Ju Seung reminds me of JUHOON of CORTIS.)
- Is this his last episode? - Seriously.
Will you be okay?
Ju Seung, you've lost your touch. You'll get into big trouble.
- It's too... - I didn't say it.
Are those three comments from you?
(Written by Lee Ju Seung)
Do you have three accounts?
People ask me if I'm his older cousin.
He has the style I'm going for these days.
- My goodness. - He's really cool.
I can be a lookalike called JUWOON.
Take a look.
(Copying an idol's style with the fashion coach)
(Embarrassed)
I feel like you'll be on "Incredible Moment."
- "Incredible Moment." - A middle-aged man who lives young.
"We heard about a middle-aged man who lives young."
"We root for him."
Take a look with confidence.
Fashion is all about taking on a new challenge.
Honestly, I thought you could pull this down a bit.
Okay.
Pull this down. There you go.
That's it.
Like this...
For goodness' sake.
I was wearing safety shorts.
Those are safety shorts.
That startled me.
This fashion comes with a downside.
He's handsome.
- Why is it a bit awkward? - Ju Seung is handsome.
Yes. He's very handsome.
Can you make a cute face?
Look at the camera effortlessly.
(Effortless)
A new host of "Popopo."
(JUHOON, I'm your older brother.)
- "Popopo." - A new host of "Popopo."
Thank you for everything, guys.
This will be his last episode.
(I'll repay you for your kindness with good work.)
This is a good item. I wish you'd wear a V-neck top.
Why don't you buy a blazer like this?
What? We found it.
What do you think?
- It suits me. - Right?
- This color suits me. - Yes.
- Let's go with this one. - I think I have a warm skin tone.
Today, I bought a check pattern blazer.
I also bought a vest...
I could wear inside the blazer...
as well as a gray beanie.
(He changes into his original outfit, )
(and puts away the clothes he won't wear.)
- Are you done? - Yes.
Let's take these items.
(He moves with the items he'll pay for.)
Sir, I'll give this a go.
- My goodness. - You need to grab this part.
I'm in a bad condition these days.
- What? - You can do pull-ups.
After 5, you get a 5-percent discount.
If you do 20, you get a 20-percent discount.
- That's incredible. - Really?
Here I go.
Martial artist, show me what you can do.
- One. - He's light.
(He's off to a light start.)
- Four percent. - He's set.
(Good luck.)
- Five percent. - He'll do ten pull-ups with ease.
(If he does 2 more, he'll get a 10-percent discount.)
Nine.
- The last one. - Ten.
Ten.
Ten percent.
(He succeeds in doing 10 pull-ups for a 10-percent discount.)
If I get a 20-percent discount, you won't make any profits.
You said the same thing last time.
- Is that so? - Yes.
Isn't it better to get a 20-percent discount?
- Give it a go. - I'll give it a go.
I'll do 20.
- It's hard to do 20. - Seriously.
Take off your shirt.
- Show me your spirits. - Look at his arms.
One, two, three...
His arm muscles look great.
(Spirits)
He has the body of a person who works out every day.
Seven, eight, nine, ten.
(He succeeds in doing 20 pull-ups for a 20-percent discount.)
Is he good at sports as well?
Is there anything he can't do?
He has all.
Well done.
(Thank you, my friend.)
- It's 78.33 dollars. - It's so cheap.
It's thanks to you.
I got a discount thanks to my friend.
Thank you.
- Bye. - Bye.
(The fashion lesson ends successfully.)
Will he take the items to a thrift store?
(He'll donate the items in a beautiful and swift manner.)
(Ju Seung and Woo Hyeon come back home.)
What? It's here.
Earlier...
This one and...
(Woo Hyeon enters the dressing room with familiarity.)
Woo Hyeon visits five times a week.
- Some friends are like that. - He takes good care of himself.
He doesn't eat spicy or salty food.
So I often make him healthy food...
for lunch and dinner.
It doesn't feel like he's cooking for his friend.
"Young master, what would you like to eat today?"
(Is he a servant?)
(He's like a servant who is cooking for his young master.)
(Young master, I'll make you something tasty.)
Today, I'll make cabbage fried rice...
and grilled half-dried red snapper.
- That sounds delicious. - That's a high-end meal.
(He makes a healthy meal for his fashion coach.)
(He scores the red snappers.)
I'll sprinkle a bit of salt.
He cooks with ease.
- Ju Seung is a talented cook. - He's a talented cook.
You don't cook a lot when you live alone.
But if your friend visits often,
it's fun to cook together.
That's incredible.
(Impressed)
(He adds meat and vegetables to the oiled pan.)
Forearm muscles.
(Using forearm muscles to beat eggs!)
- My goodness. - That's the kick.
It looks tasty.
(He pours eggs into the empty spot.)
When the eggs are almost done, turn off the heat for a second.
A bit of tonkatsu sauce and oyster sauce.
(He adds various condiments of his choice.)
Sesame oil.
It looks like your original recipe.
Ju Seung doesn't make common dishes.
(The uncommon cabbage fried rice is complete.)
All done.
(Meanwhile, Woo Hyeon cleans up without a word.)
Your friend does the dishes when you cook, right?
He does the dishes.
How generous of him.
"How generous of him?"
(How generous of young master.)
(The red snappers have turned crispy.)
They look so tasty.
Having grilled red snappers at a single man's place...
- is unbelievable. - I know.
He has lemons at home too.
I'll move the fish.
(He grabs a big plate.)
Be careful.
(A few hours ago, at a store he visited to donate clothes)
It's eight dollars.
It's nice.
He bought it for fish.
(He adds green onions to the red snapper oil.)
Ju Seung is good.
He was born with a cooking sense.
- That's right. - He has talent in cooking.
Chefs add the green onion aroma at the end.
You need to do it at the end...
so that the green onion aroma is separate from the fish aroma.
It looks delicious.
(Sniffing)
It's impressive.
(He puts fried rice in the mold.)
(Heave-ho)
- See? He has a cooking sense. - Back in the day,
people did that for omelet rice. It's nice.
- I didn't know about the mold. - It makes the fried rice clean.
(Grilled red snapper with the green onion aroma)
- Let's eat a healthy meal. - It's so healthy.
Thank you for the food.
It looks delicious.
It looks so nice.
What a presentation. I'm so curious about the taste.
(Ju Seung takes a bite first.)
It was a nice purchase.
It's nicely cooked.
It's perfect.
I hope it suits the young master's tastes.
I know. I don't know if the young master will like it.
It has a bit of the green onion aroma.
Eat it with green onion.
It's tasty.
(He takes a bite with green onion as Ju Seung says.)
(Impressed)
Gosh, it's so tasty.
It's tasty with green onion.
Do you want it? I'm going to add some spicy sauce.
I can't handle spicy food.
(He squeezes out spicy sauce over the rice.)
(The fried rice with sauce goes into his mouth.)
(Spicy)
(Woo Hyeon savors the simple taste.)
He ate with gusto, so I felt proud.
I guess it tasted nice.
The song we made...
- What? - Didn't you go there?
The guide track is out.
- Is the guide track out? - It's out.
- Will they release an album? - Did you make a song?
Does he make music?
The guide track is ready.
- Let's find the singer now. - Okay.
My friends and I meet up often.
Seeing each other continuously gave us a habit.
"Again? Is it you again? Are we going to that place again?"
We say "Again" a lot.
So we went, "Why don't we make a song that contains 'Again?'"
Woo Hyeon wrote the melody,
and I wrote the lyrics.
But we haven't found the singer yet.
(They listen to the guide track before looking for the singer.)
Oh, my.
It's a trot song.
(Smiling)
(Again, again, again, you fall in love)
(Again, again, again, you lose yourself)
- It'll be nice with a chorus. - Right?
Yourself, yourself
For goodness' sake.
That's nice.
(My friend who falls in love easily)
- I belted out that part. - Well done.
I didn't use falsetto.
(Again)
I did throat singing.
You did throat singing.
- Good. - It's nice, right?
- Yes. - I like it.
Send me the file.
I want to receive some feedback.
That's right. Let's receive some feedback.
I remembered something.
Park Ji Hyeon is your acquaintance, right?
That's right. He's the biggest expert.
- I talked to Ji Hyeon on the phone. - Okay.
He has a new album coming out...
- at the end of February. - I heard the news.
- So let's just ask for feedback. - Okay.
We don't want to pressure him.
I'm curious. It's my first time receiving feedback.
- Hello? - Ji Hyeon, are you busy?
I'm eating because it's breaktime.
- It's breaktime. - Yes.
I'll play a song over the phone.
Would you listen to it and give your feedback?
Ju Seung, did you write a song?
It isn't my work. It's by someone famous.
He's as big as Michael Jackson.
Please listen to it casually.
(He reveals his song to the trot scene's biggest expert.)
(Feeling nervous)
"Fall."
Again
It's a song that goes like this.
What's your initial reaction to the song?
(Feeling nervous)
It goes, "Fall into the gutter," right?
(Did Ji Hyeon fall into the gutter while listening to the song?)
- What? - What?
(He shares his self-written trot song with Ji Hyeon.)
(Feeling nervous)
"Fall."
It's a song that goes like this.
It goes, "Fall into the gutter," right?
No. It's not the gutter.
It's an interesting theme.
The song must intrigue you.
(Satisfied)
I don't think I'll sing this one.
(Cutting him off)
It's a song about falling into the gutter.
There's a belief that singers follow the lyrics of their songs.
Well, it's not about falling into the gutter.
- Right. - It's "Fall in love again."
- He misheard it. - I see.
But the song is great, though.
- Really? - Yes.
Then I'll send the whole song to you.
Me?
Yes. Check it out.
- "Me?" - You said it was great.
Why are you avoiding it?
Right. He kept changing his answer.
The song must not have been that catchy to you, to be honest.
- That's not true. It was great. - You liked it?
- The melody was great. - Right.
You wrote the lyrics?
- I wrote the lyrics. - You didn't like the lyrics?
The lyrics...
- I'm joking. - Just the melody was great.
- Just the melody was great. - I'm joking.
Don't give up on Ji Hyeon.
- But... - We didn't send the file yet.
- Was that why? - Don't give up on Ji Hyeon.
Our song will be out soon.
Anyway, in 2026,
I'm planning to make new challenges.
I wasn't interested in fashion,
but I'm planning to get into fashion.
I'm working as a creator as well.
Lyric writing might feel difficult,
but even if it comes to be a bit stressful,
I want to use my imagination...
to try something new.
That is why I'm challenging myself in different ways.
My future is boundless.
(Dreaming and challenging boundlessly)
(I Live Alone)
It's a pleasure to see you!
It's time to welcome in our Rainbow Live guest.
- Right. - The Running Horses special.
It's already the fourth episode.
- Gosh. - Gosh, already the fourth episode?
The fourth guest of the Running Horses special...
is the Human Vitamin who makes you feel pleasant...
the moment you see her.
The definition of loveliness.
It's Tsuki of Billlie!
- Tsuki! - Gosh!
It's the Human Vitamin!
- Gosh! - My goodness!
(Over 15 million of fancam views)
(The master of facial expressions)
(Tsuki expressed the song really well.)
(Tsuki did well to express the concept of the song.)
(Billlie's Japanese member, Tsuki)
(She worked hard to obtain advanced Korean skills.)
(She completed the marathon even with her injury...)
(and even proved her dogged spirit.)
(The passionate one with no limits, Tsuki)
- Welcome! - Hello!
- Hello! - Welcome.
Happy New Year!
Gosh!
- Move to the middle. - Right.
She's different in tone as expected.
- Right. She's different. - Gosh, I feel so nervous.
Welcome to the Rainbow Club.
Please greet our viewers.
Right!
Hello, everyone!
I'm Tsuki, and I'm from Japan!
(Welcoming her)
It's the Running Horses special.
Were you born in the Year of the Horse?
I was totally born in the Year of the Horse.
I'm going to gallop around this year.
(Neighing)
- Born in the Year of the Horse. - That's right.
(Learning Never Ends)
(Someone is sleeping under the mood lamp.)
You keep the light on?
Yes. I keep the light on because I'm scared of ghosts.
- So that's why. - Really?
(Rustling)
(Fortunately, she wakes up without any ghosts around.)
(Getting up)
(Half awake)
Hello.
I've lived alone for two years.
I'm Tsuki of Billlie!
(Feeling shy)
Up until last year, I lived in another house...
for around a year and a half.
It's been around five months since I moved here.
It hasn't been that long since you've lived alone.
Hasn't it been a while since you moved to Korea?
It's been ten years since I moved to Korea.
I've lived with my members...
and it has been two years since I've lived alone.
The previous house I lived in was a studio apartment.
I've wanted to find a place just right for me...
with a separate bedroom and living room.
I managed to find the perfect place,
and I decided to move in.
(Tsuki's bedroom is full of pink.)
I've always liked pink.
I wanted to make the room feel like a princess's room.
That is why I used lace and flower patterns.
(She looks half awake in her princess style bedroom.)
(Blanking out)
Why does my face look so puffy?
I have to get up!
(She barely manages to get out of her bedroom.)
- It isn't pink outside the bedroom. - Right.
(The living room is full of black, unlike the bedroom.)
Actually, the living room is my favorite place.
I don't like the sunlight...
and I can relax...
in a place that is dark...
as it makes me feel comfortable.
I got a black sofa, a black table,
and black curtains.
There are various black tone items in the living room.
I even painted my TV, which was completely white.
(She painted the white TV with black.)
- The TV was painted. - Right.
- I painted the TV. - Gosh!
The TV was painted?
- Yes. - Right.
- Really? - Even the sides.
Did you use spray paint?
No. There are products used for painting furniture.
I bought them,
and painted the TV with the brush.
- Really? - She's great with her hands.
(In the kitchen next to the black living room, )
(there are tastes of Korea...)
(and tastes of Japan.)
(Korean and Japanese ingredients are in the fridge together.)
Do you also go to Don Quijote when you buy condiments?
I always go there when I visit home.
Did you think only Koreans went there?
That was what I thought.
It's packed with Koreans.
- You only see Koreans there. - Right.
Right. You can only hear Korean when you go there.
There are only Koreans in the konjac jelly corner.
- Right. - On the first floor.
- They're all gathered there. - Right.
(She plops down on the black sofa right away.)
(Lying down)
(I want to lie down even more even though I'm lying down.)
(Feeling drowsy)
(She turns the TV first.)
(Struggling)
What is that?
- Is that a running machine? - Gosh!
Yes.
- It must be for walking. - It's a walking machine?
Right. On my days off,
I use that in the morning for around 30 minutes to an hour...
while watching a show or listening to music.
(Her morning routine casts away her sleep.)
(Pressing)
It's "No Other Choice."
(Focused)
"Dedication."
(Dedication?)
It's a difficult word.
(Pausing)
"Dedication."
(She picks up her phone.)
She looks up the word right away.
I see. "Dedication."
(She resumes the show after solving her curiosity.)
You're watching the show with Korean subtitles.
Right. When I don't understand a certain word,
I have to read the word that I want to look up.
That is why I have the subtitles on.
How did you study Korean at the start?
When I first came,
I stopped contacting my parents.
I did that for around six months.
Did you really have to go that far?
She didn't want to speak in Japanese.
Right. I didn't want to speak in Japanese at all.
After doing that,
I memorized 30 words each day.
I went through quizzes and such to study.
At what age did you first come to Korea?
I came when I was around 12.
She came at a really young age.
You came...
- without knowing any Korean. - Right.
You stopped contacting your parents,
- Right. - and studied alone?
Right. That's what I did.
After doing that for six months,
I learned words for everyday conversations,
and I was able to speak comfortably.
That was when I started contacting my parents again.
- Just after six months? - Right.
That must be why you're great with languages.
Why is that?
Because you stopped contacting your parents.
(Is it because he stopped contacting his parents?)
(English)
(Chinese)
(Japanese)
You're great at speaking many different languages. Chinese.
You can speak three different languages.
(The fruit of being a hardworking bad son?)
(She keeps watching the movie while using the translator.)
I hear you're wielding the ax.
"Wielding the ax?"
So she pauses it every time she looks up something.
So that's how it should be done.
(She pauses to look up another word soon after.)
(She's fully focused without taking a break.)
What?
I see.
(Stopping)
Gosh, Tsuki works so hard.
- It's making me reflect on myself. - She was bound to be good...
- Right. - studying like that.
(She's amazing.)
(Struggling)
(Shall I wash up now?)
(Brushing her teeth)
(She gets done with thoroughly brushing her teeth.)
(Walking over)
- What? - She must be heading out.
(She gets dressed in an all-black outfit.)
She really loves black.
It feels like I'm at peace when I wear black.
All of my skirts and pants are all black.
Even my tracksuits are all black.
(Even her glasses are black.)
Everything is black.
(Satisfied)
(Picking up)
(Shall I head out now?)
(Tsuki leaves the house after getting dressed in black.)
It feels a bit like "Hello Franceska."
(The youngest of the vampire family is heading somewhere?)
I thought it was a rerun of the MBC show.
("Hello Franceska")
(She heads out while showing off her dark energy.)
(Humming)
Should I get some carp bread?
(Exclaiming)
(She heads in somewhere after overcoming the temptation.)
Hello.
(Is she at a supermarket after saying hello naturally?)
When I bought things like meat online,
there were times when they weren't as fresh as...
the ones sold in supermarkets.
So when it comes to meat or vegetables,
I tend to go grocery shopping for them.
Ever since I was young,
I helped my parents with the cooking.
I got an oven recently. I bake cookies from time to time.
- I heard they're hard to make. - She goes through all that work?
- Check out the kimchi jjigae. - The kimchi jjigae looks amazing.
Right?
I make pasta or gambas al ajillo as well.
I try to make different kinds of dishes.
You must be a great cook.
(She heads into the supermarket after picking up a basket.)
Let's see.
This was the supermarket look?
Yes.
It's just in case I bump into someone.
"Tsuki isn't that pretty."
- In case that happens? - I feel hurt when that happens.
The kimchi is right here.
Aged kimchi.
She went with aged kimchi.
Pork belly with skin or pork belly.
(She heads to the meat corner after getting the kimchi.)
How many grams is this?
It's 600g.
- Would this one be better? - She's meticulous.
What would be good? There are so many of them.
- Ma'am. - Yes.
Is there thinly sliced pork belly?
Yes.
I want to make braised kimchi and pork belly rolls.
- Braised kimchi with pork belly. - Braised kimchi with pork belly.
That needs a lot of work to make.
There's pork belly with skin.
Which one would be better?
- I'll choose one for you. - That's great.
- The one that looks delicious. - Great!
I can't tell the difference.
It's best to ask the ladies at the supermarket.
Right.
- Thank you! - Here you are.
- Right. Thank you. - Thank you.
Pollack roe. I need to get some pollack roe.
Is it here?
- Ma'am, where's the pollack roe? - Yes?
- Sorry? - Where's the pollack roe?
- The what? - Pollack roe.
- Pollack roe? - Gosh!
- It's really hard to pronounce. - Over there.
- "Pollack roe." - "Pollack roe."
Pollack row?
Roe!
The pronunciation changes when the two words are together.
- "Pollack roe." - "Pollack roe."
"Pollack roe."
People will understand you much better that way.
Really?
- Pollack roe. - Right.
Thank you!
(Impressed)
It's big!
- It's plump. - Gosh. It looks tasty.
(The pollack roe looks plump.)
Okay. Thank you.
(Okay. This is it.)
If I ask the ladies there, they help me right away.
It's really convenient.
Well,
they're my seniors in life.
- I can fully trust them. - Seniors in life.
(She looks around after picking up the pollack roe.)
What is that?
(Sniffing)
Gosh.
- Gosh! - Try some.
- Really? - Yes.
- It's the tasting booth. - Thank you!
I love Korean culture.
Do they not have tasting booths in Japan?
They rarely have them.
I got so surprised.
If you go to a supermarket in Korea,
there are tasting booths with each step you take.
After a round...
- That's true. - Right.
You feel full after going through all of them.
Right. You feel full after a round.
- It's hot. Be careful. - Thank you.
Right!
It's being sold at a great price today.
(It's a taste that makes her eyes roll around.)
- It's good, isn't it? - Yes. It's good.
- Can I get one? - Would you like one?
(Can I get one?)
One?
- Thank you. - Thank you.
- Thank you. - Hope you enjoy it.
Fascinatingly enough, it tastes good there.
But it doesn't taste the same at home.
- You should eat a little. - Right.
Here it is.
Okay. For Korean cuisine.
- Hello. - Hello.
(She hurries over to the counter.)
Thank you.
Here we go.
(She meticulously puts the things into the grocery bag she brought.)
- She brought a grocery bag. - She carries that around.
She has a pretty one.
- Thank you. - Goodbye.
Bye!
Okay.
(She returns home.)
Gosh.
(Straining)
There we go.
I should try making it without looking at the recipe.
(She gets the condiments that she will be using.)
Soy sauce and cooking wine.
(I should wash my hands thoroughly as well.)
Chili powder.
(She starts cooking in earnest.)
(She pours out the chili powder without measuring it.)
I'll add some cooking wine...
and there's the sauce.
- A little bit of pepper. - Oh, good.
She seems to know what she's doing with the sauce.
- My father was a chef in the past. - Gosh.
- She must have the cooking genes. - Right.
Okay.
Roll them up.
(She neatly spreads out a slice of kimchi first.)
(She cuts the meat with scissors.)
- I learned that in Korea. - This is so nice.
Cutting meat with scissors.
(Finding her to be cute)
The strangest thing for foreigners who visit restaurants in Korea...
for the first time is the scissors on the table.
- Right. - Really?
They don't understand why the scissors are on the table.
- Others don't use scissors? - They don't.
Scissors are used only for cutting paper.
They don't understand why they are used for cutting food.
They get shocked by it.
But as K-food spread out,
scissors were so convenient with food.
- Right. - Right.
It's the best.
- Knives don't work well. - No.
You have to go back and forth so many times.
That is why many people started using scissors.
Right.
Yes.
(Rolling)
There we go.
- It looks delicious. - Okay.
Okay. There we go.
- She's so talented. - Right.
It's like mille-feuille nabe.
The "mille-feuille nabe?"
(The mille-feuille nabe-like braised kimchi is put on the stove.)
Here we go.
Okay. This looks great.
(Pouring into the bowl of sauce)
Some broth will be poured on top.
There we go. This is great.
(A generous amount of allulose for its sweetness)
- Allulose. - For its sweetness.
Okay.
- It looks good. - There we go.
Right. It looks delicious.
Right.
It's getting warmer.
I want to try this at home as it looks easy to make.
(While the braised kimchi boils...)
(Thinking)
It's too bright.
Should I give it a try?
(She gets something out of the drawer while humming.)
(She also gets something from underneath the bed.)
I can do it. I really can.
- I believe in myself. - What is that?
- What is she doing? - What is that?
As it's my day off,
I wanted to take care of my house chores.
I wanted to install the curtains.
That was why I got everything out.
Since I don't like the sunlight,
I wanted to make it as dark as possible.
- It's another layer. - Another layer?
(She gets something else out from the utility room.)
(Tsuki gets out a ladder to install the curtains.)
She has a ladder at home?
- She has a ladder at home. - I have everything.
I can do this.
(Fascinated)
Let's go.
(Climbing up)
It won't be easy.
I want to take care of everything on my own if I can.
I will accept it if I can't do it...
and call for help.
I think I'm someone who tries to get things done on my own...
until the very end.
I should give it a try first.
(She uses her bare hands without any tools.)
- It's slippery. - Use a screwdriver.
She's using her hand to drill?
- You're drilling it like this? - You're using your hand?
Some use their nails to drill it.
- Oh, like this? - You know, right?
- Totally. - And their skin would get scraped.
- Right. - That's right.
(Struggling to drive a nail with her hand)
(Loose)
(Oh, right. I forgot the braised kimchi.)
The braised kimchi.
(The braised kimchi is boiling up.)
(I should go check on the braised kimchi.)
(Checking on the braised kimchi, leaving the curtains)
It must've turned out well.
- Right? - It looks delicious.
- Right? - It looks good.
- It looks really good. - It looks good.
Yes.
- It was sweet, right? - Maybe it was too good?
(Carefully tasting it again)
It looks like it's too good.
- What? - I was wrong.
Gosh, what do I do?
It tasted too artificial.
- Why? - How can it taste bad with those?
(Serious)
Is it because of allulose?
What is the problem?
Hold on.
(The house is a mess, and her cooking isn't going well.)
I'm making braised kimchi,
and I added allulose.
But it tastes really weird.
What went wrong with it?
"This happens often." What?
"Happens often?"
"It must be because of these reasons."
"The unique aftertaste of allulose."
Exactly! The unique aftertaste.
Seriously!
The aftertaste is killing me! Darn.
That was the best Korean you used.
- Out of what I saw. - I know.
Gosh! I should've just added sugar.
- I shouldn't have bought this. - It's for syrup.
- That's for dessert. - You added allulose for dessert.
Oh, it's different?
"Add a bit of sugar, plum extract, or oligosaccharide."
"Add more doenjang or gochujang."
"Add sesame oil or perilla oil."
I should add everything. Hold on.
- Then, I'll add sesame oil. - Gosh, don't.
- You'll ruin it. - I have gochujang.
I have Cheongyang red peppers. Is it Cheongyang red pepper?
- It's Cheongyang red pepper. - She has...
- Did they go bad? - basic ingredients at home.
That's right!
Should I add sugar? But it's past its expiration date.
I should just add it.
Let's just add it.
It's okay. You won't die.
Will sugar kill you?
No, it won't.
You have a problem? No, I don't.
Just give it a try.
(Scraping all the gochujang)
- All right. - She finished it so easily.
- I know. - Right?
- It'd have taken me 2 hours. - It'd take me 2 and a half hours.
(Deep breaths)
Please...
(Gosh, please...)
(Expectant)
(With a desperate heart...)
(Crying)
(What do we do?)
(Dashing out of shock)
(Clattering)
(Laughing)
Please...
(Tsuki revived the braised kimchi that was ruined.)
(Crying)
(What do we do?)
(Dashing out of shock)
(Clattering)
(Laughing)
(Crying)
I want to try it. How does it taste that she's crying?
I want to try it too.
- I'm really curious. - I'm really curious.
- I want to taste it. - It makes me more curious.
It was the worst taste I'd ever had.
Then why did you say...
- that you have a knack for cooking? - I'm so embarrassed.
Oh, gosh. No!
Dad! Help me.
I didn't know food could be this inedible.
Seriously. Let me think.
I don't know what to do.
(Crying)
Are you crying?
Why are you crying?
Did you get a reality check?
I got a reality check. I was annoyed.
- Oh, you were annoyed. - So, you don't just cry...
when you're running.
I feel like crying.
(She bawls in front of bad food too.)
Of course. She gave it so much effort.
Oh, my. She's bawling.
It's so bad.
(She's overwhelmed because it's so bad.)
- I didn't know what to do. - Hey, you... It's like...
(What do I do now?)
I think you're the worst cook out of the members...
who visited us recently.
No, don't be prejudiced.
People will get the wrong idea. This is bad.
I'm good at cooking!
When it tastes bad,
it becomes a big better if you add lots of scallions.
- He's being considerate. - Oh, lots of scallions?
One thing for sure is that...
it'll solve everything if you add ramyeon base.
- That'd be the best. - That's true.
- I didn't know. - Ramyeon base solves everything.
- Really? - It solves everything.
I can do this.
Add water.
(Shaking mysterious powder)
Is it ramyeon base?
It's Japanese seasoning powder.
That'd be okay.
And Korean seasoning powder.
(Adding lots of Korean seasoning powder as well)
Please!
(Adding lots of chili powder as well)
That'd taste better.
She's using more sauces than the chefs in "Culinary Class Wars."
It's okay. Just...
It's okay even if you fail.
(Opening)
Let's see.
- It looks amazing, right? - I think it'll be delicious.
All right.
It's so pretty.
(Taking something)
Sprinkling.
She's even sprinkling furikake on top.
I wanted to have a proper meal.
Pollack roe?
(I can't leave out pollack roe.)
It's so cute!
That must be really delicious.
(Amazed)
(It's a must to take a photo of it.)
A photo she'll delete anyway.
(She'll delete that photo anyway.)
That's the first thing you'll delete when you run out of space.
- The landscape and food photos. - You don't even look at them.
You don't even give it a glance.
And the photos of sky come next.
(Sky photos are 2nd in line to be deleted.)
- Sky photos! - Sky photos come next.
- Then I delete my selfies too. - That's right.
In the end, you're left with photos of your dogs and cats only.
That's true.
(I did such a good job!)
(Braised kimchi with all sorts of sauces is done!)
You plated them nicely.
It's perfect.
How long did it take you to make that?
Around two and a half hours?
That's like us.
Two and a half hours?
It seems like you made kimchi during that time as well.
You could go to Japan...
- with that amount of time. - Totally.
I could go back and forth.
- You could go to Fukuoka. - It's possible.
You could go and see your dad, even.
It's totally possible to go to Japan and come back.
Thank you for the food.
(The first meal she made for herself after ups and downs)
(Trying the kimchi first)
(Crunchy)
(Then taking a big bite of meat)
It must be delicious.
It must be fine.
(Exclaiming)
- How was it? - It was good.
(She can't stop eating.)
(It's so good. I'm exhilarated.)
(Taking a bite with a big piece of pollack roe)
(Eyes going wide)
(Yes, this is it.)
(Happy)
(Applauding the braised kimchi I made)
It's delicious.
(She finished the whole braised kimchi.)
She ate them all.
(Getting up)
(She brushes her teeth right away.)
(Tsuki puts on a coat.)
Where are you going again?
You haven't installed the curtains yet.
Considering the amount of time she takes to cook,
she should get new ingredients...
and start cooking again.
She needs to get ready for dinner.
(It looks like she'll prepare dinner.)
(Shall I go out now?)
- Here we go. - She's really diligent.
- I know. She's really diligent. - She doesn't stay seated.
She must be tired by now.
She could lie down on the couch after her meal.
Hello.
- Yes, hello. - Hello.
(Going somewhere in a taxi)
The weather is great today.
(Gazing deeply)
It's a lot warmer today, right?
Yes, it's less cold now. It's warm.
Your pink shirt makes it feel like spring.
Is that so?
It's pretty.
Not many people can pull off pink.
Gosh, thank you.
While you drive around,
do you get a lot of foreign passengers?
Yes, I do.
I'm Japanese.
- You're from Japan? - Yes.
There were so many things I wanted to do in Korea.
Like going to Gyeongbokgung...
dressed in hanbok.
I wanted to try those basic things, but I haven't got the chance to.
You couldn't do it even though you've been here for ten years.
No. I want to.
You should try experiencing many things. It'll be nice.
Sure.
What's your hobby?
Hobby? It's running marathons.
- Really? - Yes.
- This is crazy. - I'm a marathon lover.
- Have you seen "Extreme84?" - Yes, I have.
The woman in that show...
Do you remember the woman who cried while running?
Oh, dear.
I think I've seen her.
- That was me. - Is that so?
It was me, sir!
The one who cried while running.
The one who bawled while running was me.
Here. Look at me.
(Do you recognize me?)
- Right? - You do look like her...
without the glasses.
- Right? - Yes.
(Feeling proud that he recognizes her)
How fascinating. I can't believe it.
We got here before we knew it while talking.
Right. It was too short.
You should've asked him to make about two more rounds.
That's hilarious.
Seriously. Don't get hurt...
and stay healthy while running.
Gosh, you too.
- Thank you, sir! - Bye.
- See you! - Have a good day.
You too!
(This way.)
(Sending off the taxi driver)
- She's so cute! - She even did the gesture.
Gosh, I've never seen something like that.
- It's a bit like a sitcom. - You're right.
In sitcoms, her skirt would be caught in the taxi door.
Right.
I've never imagined seeing someone being respectful that way.
- I've never seen such energy level. - I should learn that from her.
All right.
(Setting out with high energy)
Where is that?
(Rushing)
(Her pace gets more and more hurried.)
All right.
- Where is that? - What?
- She's going to paint. - You went to learn to paint?
Oh, meditation. She must be meditating.
Meditation?
(Being careful)
- Hello. - Hello.
(She quietly enters a mysterious place.)
- It's an atelier. - That's right! It's an atelier.
- You're learning to paint. - Yes, that's my hobby.
- All right. - All right.
(Plopping down in her seat in a familiar way)
It's my fourth time, including today.
I learn how to sketch with a pencil and coloring it.
I've been learning it step by step each day.
She did quite well.
She really did well.
It hasn't been long since I moved,
so I wanted to decorate my bedroom.
The wallpaper is white, and there's nothing on it.
Oh, she's right.
I wanted to decorate the wall with the pictures I painted.
That's why I went to an atelier.
(Glancing)
(Dabbing)
(Taking a look at the example)
(She paints the flower without hesitation.)
(Quietly coloring without saying a word)
(She paints a picture she'll put in her bedroom.)
(Soley focusing on the painting)
(Clattering)
(At home, her behavior was unpredictable.)
Actually, I talk to myself a lot...
when I'm not focusing on anything.
At least when I paint,
I can focus on it fully without any thoughts.
I'd think, "I didn't know I could be this happy."
It's a place where I can relax.
- Right. - That's important.
Yes.
(Drawing is like meditating.)
It's really good for your mental health.
That's right.
It's important to know how to focus.
She's immersed in it.
I'm super focused.
(It's as if only the picture and Tsuki existed in this world.)
(She keeps painting, forgetting to talk to herself.)
She's totally focused.
- That's right. - Mix it with green.
- With green? - Yes, and then...
- All right. - Okay.
- Amazing. - Are you done?
What do you think?
- Oh, my gosh. - What do you think?
That's the darkest one,
- and that's the bright one. - That's right.
- I colored everything. - You drew well.
- You're good. - You did a good job.
- Thank you! Yes! - It's pretty.
It's pretty.
(Moved)
- It's finally done. - Great job.
- I'm so happy. - Yes.
- Next time, I should paint that. - Yes.
Great.
- Have a safe trip home. - Thank you. Bye.
Hello.
(Showing)
- Good. - Thank you.
What? It looked like you were showing it around.
That's right. I showed it to him.
Are you selling it while carrying it around?
I wanted to show it off a bit.
I was so happy.
How should I react to that?
- "Gosh." - "Gosh."
(A painting that steals a passerby's attention)
She's so cute, though.
You should carry it carefully. It'd stain your coat.
That's right.
It did get on my coat.
(It did get on my coat.)
I see.
That was the last day of that coat.
- Goodness. - Goodness.
- That's one expensive painting. - Bye.
It's here.
(Striding somewhere while carrying an expensive painting)
(Going straight to the store she sees)
Where are you going again...
- Where is the entrance? - while carrying that?
(Cautious)
(Suddenly displaying her painting in front of someone's store)
- It suits the store. - Right?
- You're right. - That's what I thought too.
That's why I took a photo of it.
- Nice. - Right?
(Happy)
Hello!
- Where is it? - Hello.
A cooking class?
(She dropped by a nearby store since she went to the atelier.)
Is it a Japanese curry restaurant?
I came by because they said...
- I could get natto here. - Is that so?
There's a place that sells natto?
It's a restaurant specializing in natto.
There's a restaurant that specializes in natto?
(She's at a natto-specializing restaurant.)
I'll take one large box.
- One large box? Got it. - Yes.
Thank you.
(Buying big-sized natto shyly)
I'm so excited.
- I'll help you with the payment. - Sure.
I saw natto gelato too.
We do have natto gelato.
- You do? - Do you want it?
Yes.
- Yes, I'll take one. - All right.
Amazing!
- Thank you. - Natto gelato?
I can't imagine its taste.
I really wanted to try it.
(There are natto beans here and there in the gelato.)
(Drooling)
- I'll give you the gelato first. - Thank you.
Thank you for this.
(Feeling uplifted by natto gelato she's been wanting to have)
Oh, gosh. It's my first time trying it.
(Exclaiming)
(Taking a bite with high expectations)
It must be good.
Is it good?
It's good. It's really good.
It was so good.
I went to paint earlier.
- I carried the painting here. - He didn't ask.
Stop! Stop it, Tsuki!
I thought it'd be too much for you if I carried it inside.
You can show it to me.
Really? I'll bring it. One second.
- Ta-da. - It's amazing.
I should eat while looking at it.
- She's really sociable. - Nice.
She gets along with others really well.
(Super sociable Tsuki has a good time with him...)
(even though it's her first time seeing him)
She gets close with others really fast.
I know.
That was good. I finished it.
- I'll throw it for you. - Thank you.
(Thank you for the gelato.)
Yes!
I'm so happy.
How cute. Thank you.
- There's an instruction inside. - Okay.
All right.
Thank you! Bye!
(She leaves the restaurant feeling more excited.)
I'll come again. Thank you.
That was good.
- The painting you drew in one hand. - That's right!
- And natto in the other hand. - That's right.
You have the whole world...
- in your hands. - That's right.
Shall I go back now?
I'm back.
(She gets changed into something comfy as soon as she gets home.)
(Moving)
(Hurrying to the bedroom with her painting)
It might be too high to hang.
- It suits her room really well. - It suits her room.
Right?
She must've contemplated a lot to choose that...
before she painted it.
Should I put it here and put another one next to it later?
(Thinking)
It'll be pretty nice.
- Like this. - It suits the room.
Okay, over here.
(Struggling)
(Driving the pin into the wall with her whole body)
She's not hanging it in the middle?
I want to hang the picture I'm painting next to it.
Yes.
Oh, my!
It's so pretty.
(It's so pretty.)
It's pretty.
- Yes, continue painting. - I will.
Even though I painted it myself,
I thought, "Who painted this? It's so pretty."
That's how well the picture turned out.
I kept thinking that.
It's so pretty.
I wondered where to place my next painting.
It's satisfying.
That's the fun of life.
And now...
First, let's turn on the lights.
Okay. Let's get started.
(Let's see.)
- She's eating again? - She's cooking again?
(It's already time for dinner.)
- This time... - Seriously.
Let's ruin it again.
(Joking)
No!
I was confident with this one.
Cream cheese, natto,
and pollack roe.
(Cutting the cream cheese first)
(What's the next ingredient?)
(Spicy and salty salted pollack roe)
(She rolls the perilla leaves and cuts them thinly.)
(Placing one by one)
What is that?
Natto.
Oh, my.
- Oh, my gosh. So cute. - It looks delicious.
(Yes, this is it!)
Soy sauce?
That's tsuyu.
And the leftover braised kimchi.
- Nice. - It looks like a dish...
- Great. - from a popular restaurant.
It became better after boiling for a long time.
These are done.
I had to take a photo.
Will it last two weeks?
Forget about that.
You won't even remember that you took a photo of it.
Right. I need to find it.
All right.
(Tsuki's simple dinner)
(Heave-ho)
(It looks delicious.)
Dad is working.
There's a family group chat.
You don't have one?
No.
- Hi, honey. - Hi.
(Video chatting with her mother)
- That's my mom. - She's really young.
- She's young. - Your mother is really young.
- How old... - How old is she?
I think she's 53 or 54.
What about your dad?
My dad is even younger. He's 50.
- Your dad is 50? - Yes.
That's your big uncle.
Come pay respects with a bow during the holiday.
What's Dad up to?
- Look. I made dinner. - You made dinner?
What did you make?
Natto...
Natto cream cheese with pollack roe and perilla leaves...
over rice.
It doesn't look good.
It is good.
I don't like natto.
Ta-da.
It's braised kimchi.
That looks really good. I want to have rice with it.
They look like friends.
- I know. - Yes.
Try speaking in Korean.
Do you know how to say, "I want to eat it?"
I missed you.
She said something hard.
That's correct.
I want to eat it.
- I want to eat it! - Yes.
Her pronunciation is good.
What about "Thank you for the food?"
Thank you for the food.
(Thank you for the food.)
I practiced saying it really hard last time.
(She studies Korean with her mom.)
- That's your dad? - That's my dad!
Dad!
You worked hard today.
I called my parents.
I live in Korea,
my mom lives in Osaka,
and because of his work,
my dad lives in Hiroshima.
As we all live separately,
we're all lonely.
So we thought we should video call each other.
We video call each other often.
We do it almost every day these days.
You guys must miss each other a lot.
I snuck out.
I was having a team dinner.
You're going through a lot.
Do you know how to say that in Korean?
"It's all right."
- What do you mean it's all right? - "It's all right."
What's all right?
Is it "Thank you?"
"Thank you."
I got to learn about Korean culture...
through my mom and dad.
- No wonder. - So my mom would watch...
Korean period dramas or old dramas,
and I got to listen and learn Korean through them.
Your mom loves Korean dramas too, right?
It's called Jang...
- Oh, "Jewel in the Palace?" - Yes, "Jewel in the Palace!"
- "Jewel in the Palace." - Yes.
- Oh, "Jewel in the Palace?" - That's right.
I see, "Jewel in the Palace."
My father is a fan of TVXQ.
- Your father? - Yes.
- Really? - Really?
He's a fan of Shim Chang Min.
- Really? - Gosh.
You watched "Itaewon Class" a lot.
You could speak Korean a little back then.
He wanted to do the Park Sae Ro Yi hair,
but everyone was against it.
This is kind of like the Park Sae Ro Yi hair.
He's right.
Your mom is frowning.
Both of them love dramas.
So my dad wanted to visit the places...
with the memories of "Itaewon Class."
He's been saying that for years,
but he hasn't been able to go.
My mom also wanted to wear hanbok...
and go to Gyeongbokgung.
But she hasn't been able to do that either.
So this year, I want to take them around...
and experience all the things they wanted to do.
Helping them do so is one of my goals for this year.
You should bring them here.
I know. They should visit you here.
I should get back.
- All right. Hang in there. - Yes.
(May All This Year's Goals Come True)
Thank you for the video.
How was it? You were so nervous at first.
Well...
Seeing my daily life objectively,
- it was a total mess. - Not at all.
Actually, I thought of this while watching hers.
She lives in an environment where she can't help but be lonely.
- She's living in away from home, - That's right.
And Korean must feel awkward, even though she's good at it.
Your parents have high energy,
and your lifestyle...
washed away all our worries.
Professionally and personally.
I think you'll live well happily.
She really is the Human Vitamin.
We'll root for your life in Korea, Tsuki!
- Thank you! - You got it!
(We'll root for you!)
(Next story)
(I thought, "A cartoonist...")
("could be cool.")
(Someone who taught him...)
(that being a cartoonist can be amazing)
(A role model)
(Someone who had a big influence on Kian84)
(Legendary horror comic artist)
(Ito Junji)
(His childhood admiration for him...)
(led him to paying homage.)
- Ito Junji? - Yes.
(I'll help you meet Ito Junji.)
- I'll help you meet him. - You?
(Of course I thought it'd be impossible.)
(He doesn't attend external events a lot.)
(Will his dream come true?)
(His dream came true!)
(My longtime role model)
(Finally, )
(he's going to meet him.)
(I can't go empty-handed.)
(His love and care packed tightly into a lunchbox)
(Satisfied)
(Lots of love and care put into brushing as well)
(With a fluttering heart, )
(he neatly dressed in a suit, which is rare for him.)
(Is it here?)
(Gosh, this is fascinating.)
(My dream of becoming a cartoonist...)
(Mr. Junji...)
(Super nervous)
(I feel like I'm going to cry.)
(Successful fan84)
(Kang Yong is working?)
I'll be right back.
(It's still early. Is he going home already?)
(He took a half-day off...)
(to go house hunting.)
(It's already his ninth house.)
(He's done with monthly rents.)
(He'll go for a house with a large lump-sum deposit.)
(The house filled with things...)
(It's time to say goodbye.)
(I'd be happy as long as there's a place nearby where I can run.)
(The amount I'm spending...)
(on the house is different.)
(Borrowing every possible amount? No.)
(I'm going all-in.)
(Help me, seniors.)
(Help me, buddy.)
(He even gets a loan consultation to go all-in.)
(Living expenses fund, housing fund, )
(journalist credit union loan, surety insurance, )
(equal principal repayment...)
(Hasn't been employed long enough)
(Not a member of the cooperative)
Type A earned income.
(All sorts of earned income?)
(Type A earned income)
(It's exhausting to loan money.)
(It looks like his soul would get drained before going all-in.)
(But there must be a house fitting for me.)
(There are so many houses out there.)
(Only my bed will fit in here.)
(I have to go like this?)
(His conflicted feelings deepen.)
(This only fits about a fifth of my clothes.)
(To make it worse, the security deposit has gone up.)
(But my budget hasn't changed.)
(Sniffling)
(Going All out in a Never-Ending Journey)